[Log In
======](https://paywithmoon.com/login)

[Sign Up
=======](https://paywithmoon.com/signup)

Privacy Policy
==============

Effective date: January 01, 2024

**Commitment**
--------------

Moon LLC doing business as “Moon” (“Pay with Moon,” “us,” “we,” or “our”) operates the website, accessible at paywithmoon.com, as well as extensions, apps, and websites (“services”) managed by Moon, as well as products, goods, or services accessed while using said services.

Moon is committed to protecting your personal information. We take security seriously, and your privacy is our utmost concern. The information and material you share with Moon is intended to help us provide you with the best experience while using our service and is needed primarily for functionality and features.

This Privacy Policy informs you of our policies regarding the collection, use, and disclosure of personal data when you use our service, as well as the choices you have regarding your data and Moon. Earning your trust is paramount, and we believe the best way to do so is to maintain transparency in our privacy and data collection practices.

If you have further questions, don’t hesitate to reach out to us at [\[email protected\]](https://paywithmoon.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection).

**Data Collection**
-------------------

**What Data Do We Collect?**

Personal data is defined as any information that is related to an identified or identifiable person, or data containing information that can identify you or could reasonably be linked with you.

While using Moon, we may ask you to provide us with some personally identifiable data. This data may include:

* Email address
* First and last name
* Your Moon account name
* Identifiers associated with federated login providers, such as Google or Facebook

Additionally, we may collect data that is received when you interact with us, such as:

* Your IP address, data related to the device by which you interact with Moon, and data related to your use of that device
* Information generated when you use our service from collection methods like cookies and tracking analytics software (For more information, please read the section, “Cookies, Tracking, and Links”)
* Information received when you log in via a federated authentication provider like Google, Facebook, or Coinbase
* Information you submit as part of promotions, contests, or sweepstakes

**How Do We Collect Your Data?**

In most cases, Moon collects data that you provide through using our service, including at signup, when opting into emails, and when reaching out to customer support.

We also collect some information when you interact with our website, extension, social media accounts, advertisements, promotions, contests, and sweepstakes.

We also use cookies and similar tracking technologies to track user activity. For more information, read the section titled, “Cookies, Tracking, and Links”.

**How Do We Use Your Data?**

We do not sell your data.

We may access your data to:

* Determine product improvements such as new features
* Debug software errors
* Address customer complaints, concerns, and any other customer support requests

Additionally, we may use information for the following reasons:

* To provide you with marketing communications where appropriate (please see the section titled “Moon Marketing” for more details)
* To send operational emails related to your use of Moon, such as product update and transaction confirmation emails
* To run surveys
* To run promotions, contests, or sweepstakes that may require reaching out to a winner or winners
* To meet business requirements like website management, security updates, compliance and fraud prevention
* To create anonymized data for internal analytics like transaction volume and activity trend tracking which is used for things like forecasting, determining business growth, and planning marketing, promotional, and sales campaigns
* To understand how you use our products and services for product development purposes

We may also use information that is not personally identifiable for content like whitepapers, blog posts, and statistical analysis. This data will be aggregated and will never include personally identifiable details without express written consent.

Moon employees who access data for any reason highlighted above do so under strict controls. While some Moon employees may need to access customer data to maintain our services, they are prohibited from doing so unless it is necessary. Moon employees are subject to technical oversight and company-wide audit policies to ensure they aren’t inappropriately accessing your data.

For disclosures because of legal requirements, please see the section titled “Data Disclosure”.

**How Do We Store Your Data?**

Personally identifiable data you give to Moon is stored via cloud storage provided by Amazon Web Services, Inc. We sometimes access this data. This data is never hosted or stored outside of the cloud. We may sometimes access data for things like email outreach, anonymized data processing, and aggregated, anonymized data analysis.

We use recommended security protocols to encrypt all data, both in transit and at rest.

The security of your data is of utmost importance to us. But remember: no method of data transmission over the internet or electronic storage method is 100% secure. We strive to use the latest recommended practices in data security, and we continually monitor digital security best practices to upgrade our services accordingly. But we cannot guarantee your data’s absolute security.

**Limited Use of Data from the Chrome Web Store**

Moon is committed to comply with the Chrome Web Store User Data Policy, including its limited use requirements.

Under limited use requirements, Moon will:

* Only use permissions to provide or improve user-facing features
* Only transfer user data if said transfer is necessary to provide or improve the single purpose of the extension, to comply with any applicable laws, or if necessary for security purposes, such as investigating abusive behavior (please see “Data Disclosure” for more info)
* Never use or transfer user data to serve personalized, re-targeted, or interest-based advertisements
* Not allow humans to read user permissions data to which Moon has access, except in limited cases: where the user has provided consent; where it is necessary for security purposes; where it is needed to comply with applicable laws; and where anonymized data is used for internal operations

**Moon Marketing**
------------------

**Marketing Material**

Periodically, we will send marketing material related to our products, services, and partners. This material will be separate from operational emails, such as privacy policy updates, product update emails, or transactional emails.

**Promotional Offers, Sweepstakes, Giveaways and Contests**

Periodically, we may alert you about promotional offers, sweepstakes, giveaways and contests via direct correspondence like email. Your participation is entirely voluntary.

**Surveys**

We may sometimes contact you for surveys. These surveys may include forms or conversation requests. We will only use information you’ve explicitly given to us to request your participation.

We may periodically run polls and surveys on our various social media accounts and our website. We do not collect personally identifiable information from social media polls and surveys.

Participating in our surveys or polls in any form is entirely voluntary.

**Restrictions**

Moon will never use your personal and personally identifiable data to send you targeted ads.

**Cookies, Tracking, and Links**
--------------------------------

**What are Cookies and Tracking Technology?**

Cookies are files with small amounts of data which may include a unique anonymous identifier.

Tracking technologies are third-party tools like Google Analytics and MixPanel that aggregate activity and usage statistics.

**How Do We Use Cookies and Tracking Technology?**

We primarily use cookies and tracking technology to analyze and improve our services.

We may use third-party service providers to monitor and analyze the use of our products and services, as well as to track the performance of some of our digital advertisements. We use:

* **Google Analytics** – Google Analytics is an analytics service offered by Google that tracks and reports information like website traffic and ad conversions. Google may use the collected data to contextualize and personalize the ads on its own advertising network. For more information on Google’s privacy practices, please visit the Google Privacy & Terms page here: [https://policies.google.com/privacy?hl=en](https://policies.google.com/privacy?hl=en)
* **Mixpanel** – Mixpanel is an analytics service offered by Mixpanel Inc. that tracks and reports information about user interactions with web and mobile applications. You can prevent Mixpanel from using your information. Learn more about opting out here: [https://help.mixpanel.com/hc/en-us/articles/360000679006-Managing-Personal-Information#optout-users](https://help.mixpanel.com/hc/en-us/articles/360000679006-Managing-Personal-Information#optout-users)
* **The Meta pixel** – The Meta pixel is a tracking tool offered by Meta (Facebook) that helps us track conversions and analyze other data from ads on services like Facebook and Instagram. For more information on Meta’s privacy practices, please visit the Meta Data Policy page here: [https://www.facebook.com/privacy/explanation](https://www.facebook.com/privacy/explanation)
* **Zendesk –** Zendesk is a customer service application. We use session cookies with Zendesk to provide a better customer service experience. For more information on Zendesk’s privacy practices, please visit the Zendesk privacy policy here: [https://www.zendesk.com/company/agreements-and-terms/](https://www.zendesk.com/company/agreements-and-terms/)
* **Hotjar** – Hotjar is an analytics service offered by Hotjar Ltd. Hotjar tracks user behavior on our web pages. For more information about Hotjar’s privacy practices, please visit the Hotjar Privacy Policy here: [https://www.hotjar.com/legal/policies/privacy](https://www.hotjar.com/legal/policies/privacy)
* **Fullstory** – Fullstory is a visual analytics service. Fullstory tracks user behavior on our web pages. For more information about Fullstory’s privacy practices, as well as how to opt out of Fullstory tracking, please visit the Fullstory Privacy Policy here: [https://www.fullstory.com/legal/privacy-policy/](https://www.fullstory.com/legal/privacy-policy/)
* **OpenReplay** - OpenReplay is a visual analytics service. OpenReplay tracks user behavior on our web pages. For more information about Fullstory’s privacy practices, as well as how to opt out of OpenReplay tracking, please visit the OpenReplay Privacy Policy here: [https://openreplay.com/legal/privacy.html](https://openreplay.com/legal/privacy.html)

You can instruct your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is sent.

**Links to Other Sites**

Like the linked policies above, we may sometimes have links to other sites that are not operated by us. If you click on a third-party link, you will be directed to that party’s website or service. We strongly advise that you review the Privacy Policy of every site you visit.

**Data Disclosure**
-------------------

We may disclose information that is personally identifiable under certain circumstances. These can include:

* To comply with a legal obligation on a court order
* To protect the personal safety of users of our service or the public
* To protect and defend the rights or property of Moon LLC
* To protect against legal liability where applicable

**Data Transfer**
-----------------

Moon is based in the United States but we live in an increasingly globalized world. Because of this, your personal data may be transferred to, stored, or processed in other countries. Regardless of the privacy or data protection laws of other countries, we secure and protect your personal data in accordance with this Privacy Notice and all applicable laws.

**Your Data Protection Rights**
-------------------------------

You have rights to your data and personal information that we collect. In most cases, we will respond to your request within a calendar month, but most likely much sooner. For more information on how to reach us, please refer to the “Contact Us” section below:

* Right to be informed – You can request to obtain information about the data processing activities we undertake
* Right of access – you can request to obtain a copy of your personal data
* Right to rectification – You can request to have inaccurate personal data fixed
* Right to erasure/deletion – You can request to have your personal data erased
* Right to restriction – You can request that we restrict the processing of your personal data
* Right to object – You can object to the processing of your personal data
* Right to data portability – You can request a copy of your data to provide to another service of your choice

Moon users who are residents of California have additional data protection rights in accordance with the California Consumer Privacy Act. These include the right to know:

* The categories of personal information collected
* The categories of sources from which the personal information is collected
* Our business purposes for collecting personal information
* The categories of third parties with whom we share personal information
* The specific piece or pieces of personal information we have collected about you

For more information on how to reach us, please refer to the “Contact Us” section below.

**Children’s Privacy**
----------------------

Our products and services are not directed to people under 18. We do not knowingly collect any personal information from people under 18.

If you are a parent or guardian and you believe that your child has or your children have provided us with personal information, please contact us at [\[email protected\]](https://paywithmoon.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection). We will take steps to remove that information from our servers.

**Changes to This Privacy Notice**
----------------------------------

From time to time, we may update this privacy notice. We will place a notice on our site when we make material changes and update the “effective date” at the top of this page.

We may also attempt to notify you of any changes via email.

We encourage that you review this privacy notice periodically for changes. Changes are effective when they are posted to this page.

**Contact Us**
--------------

At Moon, we’re committed to ensuring your data is secure and your privacy is ensured. We continually review our privacy practices and security measures to both protect our users and remain compliant with applicable laws.

If you have questions, comments, or would like to exercise your data rights in accordance with our privacy notice and applicable laws, you can:

* Email us: [\[email protected\]](https://paywithmoon.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)
* Write to us at:  
    415 Madison Avenue 4th Floor, New York, New York 10017

To contact our Data Protection Officer, you can:

* Email: [\[email protected\]](https://paywithmoon.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)

**For Data Subjects in the EU**

We appointed GDPR-Rep.eu as representative according to Art 27 GDPR. If you want to make use of your GDPR data privacy rights, please visit: [https://prighter.com/q/17491075](https://prighter.com/q/17491075)

PrighterGDPR-Rep by Maetzler Rechtsanwalts GmbH & Co KG  
Schellinggasse 3/10  
1010 Vienna, Austria

‍
-

---

© 2024 Moon LLC All Rights Reserved

The Moon Visa® Card is issued by our partner Financial Institutions, pursuant to a license from Visa.

Cards may be spent across 40M+ merchants that accept Visa cards. Some restrictions apply. See [Terms & Conditions](https://paywithmoon.com/terms-conditions) for details.
